Set the sails! Top two!
Let's find the next island! Whoa!
Hey, come on, Luffy!
Can't we rest for a little while?
You're a little too relaxed.
Listen, that attitude isn't going
to get us very far on these seas.
I don't think I want to hear this.
The waves look a little too strange
for comfort, so it's back to work.
Turn to port!
Anything for you, Nami dear!
Do you see?
It's full speed ahead!
This doesn't look good for us!
There's something in the wave!
Is that the breeze? No!
Those are sea monkeys!
He doesn't seem to be here, Vice Admiral.
I know that already, you imbecile.
I'm asking you where the hell he went.
Since his bicycle is missing
too, he probably went to sea.
Contact the five Elder Stars. Sir.
Oh, pardon me, coming through.
We should expect this
sort of thing by now.
He's likely just sightseeing again.
Be that as it may,
don't you think he should show a
bit more respect for his position?
We can't have him wondering
about whenever he sees fit.
Admiral Aokiji is one of Navy Headquarters'
ultimate powerhouses, after all.
Can't say I'm surprised to see
a bounty on this kid's head.
His whole family's full of troublemakers.
Thank you.